Frances Benjamin Johnston Collection, 1935-1938 P0006
Frances Benjamin Johnston Collection, 1935-1938
- Frances Benjamin Johnston Collection, 1935-1938., Items: 2,280 images. Approximately 3.57 Linear Feet. Nine document boxes and five drawers in map case.
  - Chowan County: Edenton: Graham House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Printbox 2, Bwpprint P0006/0063)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2197.
  - Chowan County: Edenton: Hayes Plantation, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 21 images (Printbox 2, Bwpprint P0006/0064)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2162-2168; Includes one framed print.
  - Chowan County: Edenton: Hayes Plantation, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 3 images (Flatfile 1, Oimage P0006/0065)
    NC2163, NC2168
  - Chowan County: Edenton: Houses, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 3 images (Printbox 2, Bwpprint P0006/0066)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2181-2183.
  - Chowan County: Edenton: Mulberry Hill (Clement Blount house, circa 1810), circa 25451941, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 7 images (Printbox 2, Bwpprint P0006/0067)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2185-2189.
  - Chowan County: Edenton: Mulberry Hill (Clement Blount house), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 4 images (Flatfile 1, Oimage P0006/0068)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2188
  - Chowan County: Edenton: Saint Paul's Episcopal Church, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 5 images (Printbox 2, Bwpprint P0006/0069)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2191-2195.
  - Chowan County: Edenton: Saint Paul's Episcopal Church, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 images (Flatfile 1, Oimage P0006/0070)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2195.
  - Chowan County: Edenton: Sandy Point, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Printbox 2, Bwpprint P0006/0071)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2196.
  - Chowan County: Edenton: Sandy Point, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 images (Flatfile 1, Oimage P0006/0072)
  - Cleavland County: Kings Mountain: Henry Howser House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints (Printbox 2, Bwpprint P0006/0073)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2529-2533.
  - Craven County: New Bern: Ashford House (185 Polk Street), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 images (Printbox 2, Bwpprint P0006/0074)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2288-2289.
  - Craven County: New Bern: Bellair, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints (Printbox 2, Bwpprint P0006/0075)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2200-2202.
  - Craven County: New Bern: Bellair, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints (Flatfile 2, Oimage P0006/0076)
  - Craven County: New Bern: Burns House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Printbox 2, Bwpprint P0006/0077)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2276.
  - Craven County: New Bern: Coor-Gaston House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Printbox 2, Bwpprint P0006/0078)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2277.
  - Craven County: New Bern: Coor-Gaston House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Flatfile 2, Oimage P0006/0079)
  - Craven County: New Bern: Door of Jones-Jarvis House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Printbox 2, Bwpprint P0006/0080)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2255.
  - Craven County: New Bern: Duffy House on Middle Street, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 3 images (Printbox 2, Bwpprint P0006/0081)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2239-2241.
  - Craven County: New Bern: Eubank Street House (Blackwell-Bray House c: 1774), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints (Printbox 2, Bwpprint P0006/0082)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC22843.
  - Craven County: New Bern: Eubank Street House (Blackwell-Bray House), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Flatfile 2, Oimage P0006/0083)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2243.
  - Craven County: New Bern: First Presbyterian Church, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints (Printbox 2, Bwpprint P0006/0084)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2252-2254.
  - Craven County: New Bern: First Presbyterian Church, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Flatfile 2, Oimage P0006/0085)
  - Craven County: New Bern: Hanff House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Printbox 2, Bwpprint P0006/0086)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2282.
  - Craven County: New Bern: Hollister House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 images (Printbox 2, Bwpprint P0006/0087)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2285.
  - Craven County: New Bern: Hollister House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 images (Flatfile 2, Oimage P0006/0088)
  - Craven County: New Bern: Isaac Taylor House (Nixon House), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 4 images (Printbox 2, Bwpprint P0006/0089)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2250-2251.
  - Craven County: New Bern: Isaac Taylor House (Nixon House), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Flatfile 2, Oimage P0006/0090)
  - Craven County: New Bern: James Washington Bryan House and Law Office, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 4 images (Printbox 2, Bwpprint P0006/0091)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2203-2205.
  - Craven County: New Bern: James Washington Bryan House and Law Office, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Flatfile 2, Oimage P0006/0092)
  - Craven County: New Bern: Jenkins-Duffy-Stallings House on Johnston Street, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 images (Printbox 2, Bwpprint P0006/0093)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2232.
  - Craven County: New Bern: Jenkins-Duffy-Stallings House on Johnston Street, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Flatfile 2, Oimage P0006/0094)
  - Craven County: New Bern: John Wright Stanley House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 4 images (Printbox 2, Bwpprint P0006/0095)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2258-2262.
  - Craven County: New Bern: John Wright Stanley House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 images (Flatfile 2, Oimage P0006/0096)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2259, 2262
  - Craven County: New Bern: Judge Donnell House and Office, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 13 images (Printbox 2, Bwpprint P0006/0097)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2229-2236.
  - Craven County: New Bern: Judge Donnell House and Office, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 3 images (Flatfile 2, Oimage P0006/0098)
  - Craven County: New Bern: Lassiter House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Printbox 2, Bwpprint P0006/0099)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2246.
  - Craven County: New Bern: Louisana-House (Dawson-Clark House), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Printbox 2, Bwpprint P0006/0100)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2286.
  - Craven County: New Bern: Masonic Lodge, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 3 images (Printbox 2, Bwpprint P0006/0101)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2242-2249.
  - Craven County: New Bern: Houses, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 8 images (Printbox 2, Bwpprint P0006/0102)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2278-2290.
  - Craven County: New Bern: Mrs. Harkfield's Gate, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Printbox 2, Bwpprint P0006/0103)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2245.
  - Craven County: New Bern: New Bern Academy, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 images (Printbox 2, Bwpprint P0006/0104)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2198-2199.
  - Craven County: New Bern: New Bern Academy, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Flatfile 2, Oimage P0006/0105)
  - Craven County: New Bern: Saint Paul's Catholic Center, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 images (Printbox 2, Bwpprint P0006/0106)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2257-2258.
  - Craven County: New Bern: Smallwood House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 22 images (Printbox 2, Bwpprint P0006/0107)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2269-2271; Includes one framed print.
  - Craven County: New Bern: Smallwood House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 5 images (Flatfile 2, Oimage P0006/0108)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2266.
  - Craven County: New Bern: Smallwood House and office (120 Craven Street), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 images (Printbox 2, Bwpprint P0006/0109)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2280.
  - Craven County: New Bern: Swert House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 images (Printbox 2, Bwpprint P0006/0110)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2274.
  - Craven County: New Bern: Tryon Place West Wing, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Printbox 2, Bwpprint P0006/0111)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2291.
  - Cumberland County: Fayetteville: Cool Springs, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 4 images (Printbox 3, Bwpprint P0006/0112)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2293, NC2295, NC2296, NC2297; Has two copy negatives.
  - Cumberland County: Fayetteville: Cool Springs, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints (Flatfile 2, Oimage P0006/0113)
  - Cumberland County: Fayetteville: First Presbyterian Church, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 images (Printbox 3, Bwpprint P0006/0114)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2312, NC2315.
  - Cumberland County: Fayetteville: Halliday-Williams House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 4 images (Printbox 3, Bwpprint P0006/0115)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2317, NC2319, NC2320; Has three copy negatives.
  - Cumberland County: Fayetteville: Halliday-Williams House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints (Flatfile 2, Oimage P0006/0116)
  - Cumberland County: Fayetteville: Kyle House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 images (Printbox 3, Bwpprint P0006/0117)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2301-2302.
  - Cumberland County: Fayetteville: MacPherson Presbyterian Church, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Printbox 3, Bwpprint P0006/0118)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2316.
  - Cumberland County: Fayetteville: Market House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 images (Printbox 3, Bwpprint P0006/0119)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2306-2307.
  - Cumberland County: Fayetteville: Houses [miscellaneous], circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 3 images (Printbox 3, Bwpprint P0006/0120)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2298-2300.
  - Cumberland County: Fayetteville: Powell House (Old State Bank of North Carolina), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 images (Printbox 3, Bwpprint P0006/0121)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2304.
  - Cumberland County: Fayetteville: Powell House (Old State Bank of North Carolina), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints (Flatfile 2, Oimage P0006/0122)
  - Currituck County: Moyock: Twin Houses, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Printbox 3, Bwpprint P0006/0123)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2323.
  - Davidson County: Old Tavern, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 images (Printbox 3, Bwpprint P0006/0124)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2325-2326.
  - Davie County: Cooleemee Plantation, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 4 images (Printbox 3, Bwpprint P0006/0125)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2327, NC2328, NC2330.
  - Davie County: Cooleemee Plantation, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints (Flatfile 2, Oimage P0006/0126)
  - Duplin County: Buck Hill: Buckner Hill House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 4 images (Printbox 3, Bwpprint P0006/0127)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2353-2356.
  - Durham County: Durham: Duke Homestead and Tobacco Barn, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 5 images (Printbox 3, Bwpprint P0006/0128)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2335-2337.
  - Durham County: Durham: Duke University Chapel, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 22 images (Printbox 3, Bwpprint P0006/0129)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC1948-1958.
  - Durham County: Durham: Kilgo Hall, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Printbox 3, Bwpprint P0006/0130)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2347.
  - Durham County: Stagville: Fairntosh Plantation, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 3 images (Printbox 3, Bwpprint P0006/0131)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2331, NC2333, NC2334.
  - Durham County: Stagville: Fairntosh Plantation, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints (Flatfile 2, Oimage P0006/0132)
  - Edgecombe County: Old Sparta: Bracebridge Hall, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 6 images (Printbox 3, Bwpprint P0006/0133)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2372; Includes two copy negatives; Includes one framed print.
  - Edgecombe County: Old Sparta: Bracebridge Hall, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints (Flatfile 2, Oimage P0006/0134)
  - Edgecombe County: Old Sparta: Piney Prospect (Peter Evans House), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 3 images (Printbox 3, Bwpprint P0006/0135)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2369-2370.
  - Edgecombe County: Old Sparta: Piney Prospect (Peter Evans House), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints (Flatfile 2, Oimage P0006/0136)
  - Edgecombe County: Tarboro: Best House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 10 images (Printbox 3, Bwpprint P0006/0137)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2375-2380; Includes two copy negatives; Includes two framed prints.
  - Edgecombe County: Tarboro: Best House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints (Flatfile 2, Oimage P0006/0138)
  - Edgecombe County: Tarboro: Dozier House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 10 images (Printbox 3, Bwpprint P0006/0139)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2357-2362; Includes one copy negative.
  - Edgecombe County: Tarboro: Dozier House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints (Flatfile 2, Oimage P0006/0140)
  - Edgecombe County: Tarboro: Norfleet Farm and Cotton Press, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 5 images (Printbox 3, Bwpprint P0006/0141)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2363, NC2365, NC2366; Includes one copy negatives; Includes one framed print.
  - Edgecombe County: Tarboro: Norfleet Farm and Cotton Press, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints (Flatfile 2, Oimage P0006/0142)
  - Forsyth County: Old Town: Gemein House (Meeting House and Parsonage), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 7 images (Printbox 3, Bwpprint P0006/0143)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2452-2465.
  - Forsyth County: Old Town: Gemein House (Meeting House and Parsonage), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints (Flatfile 3, Oimage P0006/0144)
  - Forsyth County: Old Town: Stone House (Bethabara Parsonage), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 images (Printbox 3, Bwpprint P0006/0145)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2467-2468.
  - Forsyth County: Winston-Salem (Old Salem): Belo, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 9 images (Printbox 3, Bwpprint P0006/0146)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2405-2408.
  - Forsyth County: Winston-Salem (Old Salem): Belo, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints (Flatfile 3, Oimage P0006/0147)
  - Forsyth County: Winston-Salem (Old Salem): Blum House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Printbox 3, Bwpprint P0006/0148)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2412.
  - Forsyth County: Winston-Salem (Old Salem): Boy's School (Wachovia History Museum), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 3 images (Printbox 3, Bwpprint P0006/0149)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2445-2447.
  - Forsyth County: Winston-Salem (Old Salem): Chimney House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 13 images (Printbox 3, Bwpprint P0006/0150)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2413-2421.
  - Forsyth County: Winston-Salem (Old Salem): Chimney House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints (Flatfile 3, Oimage P0006/0151)
  - Forsyth County: Winston-Salem (Old Salem): Fourth House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 4 images (Printbox 3, Bwpprint P0006/0152)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2422-2423.
  - Forsyth County: Winston-Salem (Old Salem): Home Moravian Church, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 3 images (Printbox 3, Bwpprint P0006/0153)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2433, NC2457, NC2459.
  - Forsyth County: Winston-Salem (Old Salem): Home Moravian Church, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints (Flatfile 3, Oimage P0006/0154)
  - Forsyth County: Winston-Salem (Old Salem): John H. Boner House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Printbox 3, Bwpprint P0006/0155)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2411.
  - Forsyth County: Winston-Salem (Old Salem): John Volger House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 images (Printbox 3, Bwpprint P0006/0156)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: 2469-2470.
  - Forsyth County: Winston-Salem (Old Salem): John Volger House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints (Flatfile 3, Oimage P0006/0157)
  - Forsyth County: Winston-Salem (Old Salem): Salem College, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 6 images (Printbox 3, Bwpprint P0006/0158)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2435, NC2439, NC2440, NC2442.
  - Forsyth County: Winston-Salem (Old Salem): Salem House (Inspector's House), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Printbox 3, Bwpprint P0006/0159)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2443.
  - Forsyth County: Winston-Salem (Old Salem): Salem House (Inspector's House), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints (Flatfile 3, Oimage P0006/0160)
  - Forsyth County: Winston-Salem (Old Salem): Salem Tavern (Washington Tavern), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 images (Printbox 3, Bwpprint P0006/0161)
    Includes one copy negative; Includes one framed print.
  - Forsyth County: Winston-Salem (Old Salem): Salem Tavern (Washington Tavern), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints (Flatfile 3, Oimage P0006/0162)
  - Forsyth County: Winston-Salem (Old Salem): Single Brothers' House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 6 images (Printbox 3, Bwpprint P0006/0163)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2437, NC3438, NC2444, NC2448, NC2449, NC2450.
  - Forsyth County: Winston-Salem: Houses, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 8 images (Printbox 3, Bwpprint P0006/0164)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2425-2432, NC2451.
  - Franklin County: Centerville: Casine Plantation, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 3 images (Printbox 3, Bwpprint P0006/0165)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2392-2394.
  - Franklin County: Louisburg: Falconner House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 3 images (Printbox 3, Bwpprint P0006/0166)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2385.
  - Franklin County: Louisburg: Fenner House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Printbox 3, Bwpprint P0006/0167)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2386.
  - Franklin County: Louisburg: Foster House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 images (Printbox 3, Bwpprint P0006/0168)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: NC2388-2389.
  - Franklin County: Louisburg: Foster House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Flatfile 3, Oimage P0006/0169)
  - Franklin County: Louisburg: Green Hill, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 5 images (Printbox 3, Bwpprint P0006/0170)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2395-2398.
  - Franklin County: Louisburg: Peggy Wright House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 3 images (Printbox 3, Bwpprint P0006/0171)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2402-2404; Includes one copy negative.
  - Franklin County: Louisburg: Peggy Wright House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Flatfile 3, Oimage P0006/0172)
    Original (Johnston) negative number: 2899.
  - Franklin County: Louisburg: Person Place, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 3 images (Printbox 3, Bwpprint P0006/0173)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2390-2391.
  - Franklin County: Louisburg: Polly Wright House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 3 images (Printbox 3, Bwpprint P0006/0174)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2383.
  - Franklin County: Louisburg: Travelers Rest, A.J. Wilson's Place, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 3 images (Printbox 3, Bwpprint P0006/0175)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2400-2401.
  - Franklin County: Louisburg: Travelers Rest, A.J. Wilson's Place, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Flatfile 3, Oimage P0006/0176)
    Johnston number 2818.
  - Franklin County: Rocky Ford: Stone House (Rock House), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Printbox 3, Bwpprint P0006/0177)
    Johnston numbers NC2399.
  - Gaston County: Heyel House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 images (Printbox 4, Bwpprint P0006/0178)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2496-2497.
  - Gaston County: John Moore House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Printbox 4, Bwpprint P0006/0179)
    Johnston number: 2488.
  - Gaston County: John Smith House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Printbox 4, Bwpprint P0006/0180)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2483.
  - Gaston County: Oak Grove, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 11 images (Printbox 4, Bwpprint P0006/0181)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2491-2495; Includes two copy negatives.
  - Gaston County: Oak Grove (built circa 1782), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 1 image (Flatfile 3, Oimage P0006/0182)
  - Gaston County: Thomas Rhyne House (1799), circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 2 images (Flatfile 3, Oimage P0006/0183)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2486-2487.
  - Gaston County: Dallas: Mason House, circa 1935-1938, Black-and-White Photographic Prints; 3 images (Printbox 4, Bwpprint P0006/0184)
    Original (Johnston) negative numbers: NC2479-2481.